George Robinson

Email/Telephone: georgejohnrobinson@gmail.com / +447425244700

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/george-robinson-

Profile

I am an experienced teacher relocating to central London in September 2022. I have a good amount of experience working in inner-city locations, including St Johns Wood, and central Southampton. I have taught children with a variety of special, emotional and behavioural needs as well as children with little or no English. I have worked as a supply teacher previously and know what to expect.

Education

University of Wales Trinity Saint David | Carmarthen, Wales

Sep 2013 - Aug 2016

BA (Hons) Primary Education with QTS | Second Class with Honours

Queen Mary's College | Basingstoke, Hampshire

Sep 2011 - Aug 2013

A level | Business Studies (B), Media Studies (C), Mathematics (D)

The Downs School | Compton, Berkshire

Sep 2006 - Aug 2011

GCSEs | 10 GCSEs grade C and above, including English and Mathematics

Work Experience

Supply Teacher | Time Plan Education | London

Sep 2022 - Current

- Short and long-term supply for a variety of schools in London.
- Most experience in EYFS and some in KS1.

Teacher | Banister Primary School | Southampton

Sep 2018 - Aug 2022

- Taught as a teacher in reception for four years.
- · Co-led EYFS.
- Lead Geography for the school.
- Helped implement the new EYFS.
- Worked with children with acute special needs and physical disabilities.
- Worked as well as part of an ever-changing EYFS team.

Supply Teacher | Teaching Personnel | Hampshire

Sep 2017-Aug 2018

- Taught in a school in Wiltshire on long term supply from Jan 21-Jul 21.
- Gained experience teaching in different settings daily.
- Experienced working in year 1 and 2.
- Worked with children with additional behavioural needs.

Teacher | Robinsfield Infant School | St Johns Wood, London

Sep 2016 - Aug 2017

- Completed my NQT year.
- Worked with children from a wide variety of backgrounds.
- Learnt how to manage my workload effectively.

References

Banister Primary School

Name: Kate Vincent, Head teacher

Email/Phone: head@banisterschool.co.uk / 02380393313

Teaching Personnel

Email/Phone: recadmin@teachingpersonnel.com / 01707386444